(Howard:)Okay.
Are you from the Star Wars universe?
(Leonard:)Yes.
- Were you in the original trilogy?
- Yes.
(Howard:)Is there a picture of you in my wallet
wearing a metal bikini?
(Leonard:)God, I hope not.
(Leonard:)- No, I'm not Princess Leia.
- Okay, my turn.
Are you in all six Star Wars movies?
(Raj(finding a large quantity of condoms):)- Yes.
- Interesting.
(Raj:)- Are you a droid?
- Yes.
(Raj:)Do you kind of look like a shiny Sheldon?
(Leonard:)Yes.
- C-3P0.
- You got it.
(Sheldon:)That's preposterous.
I do not resemble C-3P0.
(Sheldon:)Don't get me wrong, I'm flattered,
I just don't see it.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Leslie Winkle. Ahem.
(Howard(phone rings):)You've reached Friends with Benefits.
For a booty call, press 1 now.
(Sheldon:)What exactly does that expression mean,
"friends with benefits"?